[Music]
Hey, I'm the sweet brunette.
And I'm the dirty blonde.
And this be iCarly.
Okay. A fan of iCarly... ...
Wrote to us right here
at iCarly.com... ...
And said this:
"So I asked my parents
for a new game station,
"but all they got me were
two wireless controllers.
"How can I play a game "if all
I got was two controllers?"
Well, Robert, first of
all, let me just say
that your parents are the worst.
They're bad people.
But the good news is... ...
If you have two controllers...
...You can still play some
pretty rockin' video games.
Even without a game station.
Let's show Robert how.
Well, okay.
[Applause]
Now, as you can see...
...Sam and I
have two wireless controllers.
We may not have a game
station to go with them...
...But we do have...
A vicious army of raw eggs.
So vicious.
They make me want to eat them.
Yes. Look at them.
Look at them.
Controllers ready.
Begin!
Oh. Yeah!
Gotcha!
Get that one! Look out!
Bam!
Game over.
[Siren blaring]
Whoa.
Yeah.
That sound means it's time for...
Messin' with Lewbert.
Woo! That's right!
It is.
Oh, yeah.
Now, you all know the nasty
doorman in my building.
a fake soda machine.
And yesterday, we put
it in the hallway
outside Carly's apartment.
Freddie, show them what happened.
Showin' them.
What the--soda machine.
Hey, who put this soda machine
here without my permission, huh?
And now it's time for
a little surprise.
Come on.
I want my diet root beer.
[Screams]
In five, four, three, two...
[music]
I know you see
somehow the world
will change for me
and be so wonderful
live life, breathe air
I know somehow
we're gonna get there
and feel so wonderful
it's all for real
I'm telling you
just how I feel
so wake up
the members of my nation
it's your time to be
there's no chance
unless you take one
and a time to see
the brighter side
of every situation
some things are meant to be
so give your best
So, you ready to hear my
brilliant idea for iCarly?
What?
Bikini dog food fight.
What's a bikini dog food fight?
We get Gibby and some other
guy, make 'em put on bikinis
and fight with dog food.
That's humiliating and gross.
I know.
Hey, Gibson.
Over here. Front and center.
Whassup?
Run, Gibby.
What's gonna happen?
Listen, I have a vision.
A vision of what?
You and some other loser...
Wearing bikinis...
Fighting...With dog food.
Gibby!
No.
I don't want-- get back here!
I don't wanna wear a bikini
and fight some other loser
with dog food.
Why not?
I have some dignity.
Since when?
No.
Come on.
Just try this on.
I'm not gonna try it on.
Leave me alone, Sam.
Give me the bikini, Sam.
What's going on? Hey.
What you doin'?
Hey.
Hi.
You guys ever watch Totally Teri
on the Dingo channel?
No. Gross.
What?
'Cause last night my little
brother was watching it
and they ripped off one
of your iCarly bits.
What did they do?
One of the stars of the show
hit a button and you heard
"random jumping"
and then music played, lights flashed,
and they jumped all around.
Dude, that's exactly the
same as random dancing.
That's what I'm sayin'.
They ripped off iCarly.
You guys should do something about it.
Yup. You should.
Can you believe this?
We don't know they stole from us.
Maybe it was just a coincidence.
Oh, come on.
We've been doing random dancing
on iCarly for two years,
now some show on the Dingo channel
starts doing random jumping
and you think that's a coincidence?
I don't know.
Maybe there was similar, you know...
Okay. No fighting,
no dog food, but I will
wear the bikini top.
[Music]
I know.
I'll wear a wig, and that way,
Devon will never know it's me.
That's a brilliant idea.
And by brilliant, I mean ridiculous.
Burn.
[Insincere laughter]
Hey, whatchoo guys watchin'?
The Dingo channel.
Some hideous show called Totally Teri.
I hate all those shows
on the Dingo channel.
The jokes are so stupid, and
they always make the grown-ups
look like buffoons.
You forgot to put your pants on again.
Oh, my God.
Man, there's not one restaurant
in Seattle that delivers
fried chicken.
Pay attention.
Let's watch the show.
So, why are you guys
watching that anyway?
'Cause some kids at school
told us the show Totally Teri
has been copying stuff
we do on iCarly.
Wouldn't surprise me.
Dingo channel is run by freaks.
What do you mean?
Well, you know the guy who
started it, like 60 years ago?
Charles Dingo?
Yeah.
I heard that when he died
of some rare disease,
they froze his head and they've
kept it in a special freezer
to this day.
Why would they wanna keep Charles
Dingo's head in a freezer?
So that in the future,
when they find a cure,
they can unfreeze it and
re-attach it to a robot body.
And I read online that
they keep the frozen head
somewhere deep in the
bowels of Dingo studios.
Okay, first, there's no way
that's true, and second,
I can't believe you said bowels
and please never say it again.
You're such a priss.
The prissiest.
Now, shhh, it's back on.
What are you doing?
Playing a joke on my doorman, Rupert.
His doorman Rupert?
Uh, that sounds a lot like Lewbert.
Yeah.
Ewww, look at that
wart on Rupert's face.
Hey, there's a wart on Rupert's face.
Yeah, just like Lewbert's.
Just not as plump.
Well, yeah, but still.
Now, watch what happens when
Rupert tries to buy something
outta that snack machine.
[Screaming]
Two hands just popped
outta that snack machine.
Yeah, where have we seen that before?
They ripped off iCarly.
No chiz.
You guys watchin'?
Yeah.
They stole "messin'
with Lewbert."
And random dancing.
Those Dingo people are dead.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna go find 'em and
kick them in their dingos.
Dingo studios is in Hollywood.
Which is like 900 miles from here.
[Music]
Okay, look, I think it's really jank
that they're rippin' off iCarly,
but I can't just drop everything
and drive you guys 900
miles to Dingo studios.
When we get there, maybe
you could find the head
of Charles Dingo.
The frozen head.
We leave at midnight.
[Music]
All right, here you go.
There's your beds, your bathroom.
What's that?
Uh, just some tape.
Hey, you said this room had
a great view of Hollywood.
It does.
Hey, Hollywood, wake up.
That's Hollywood right there.
Bye.
Could I borrow some underwear?
No.
Close it. Close it. Close it.
Close it. Close it.
What?
This is the nice hotel
your mom recommended?
This is where she stays
when she comes to town.
Why?
The plastic surgeon
works out of room 210.
All right, whatever.
Let's just figure out how we're
gonna get into Dingo studios.
I got that covered.
I went online and found a
photo of a Dingo I.D. Badge
and I made laminated copies
with our pictures for us.
One for Carly, Spencer and Sam.
Cool.
Nice work, Fredley.
And I found this online tour
of the main Dingo building.
The Totally Teri writers' room is
on the third floor, West Side.
Perfect.
We'll use these to get inside...
...And then we can find
those brain-dead writers and
start smackin' 'em around
for rippin' off iCarly.
Hey, hey, does that
online tour of Dingo
show how to get to the basement?
Yeah, why?
You gonna do a little
frozen head huntin'?
A little frozen head findin'.
I told you guys, I
looked it up and I found
three different articles
where the vice president
of the studio said that
story about Charles Dingo's
frozen head isn't true.
Of course, they say that.
They wanna keep it a secret.
'Cause how would it look
if people found out
that a kids' network has their
leader's head stuck in a freezer?
I hear the head is somewhere
deep in the bowels
of the main Dingo building.
The bowels?
See, I said it was in the bowels too.
Okay, next person who says
bowels sleeps in the bathtub.
Bowels. I got the bathtub.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[Music]
Here it is.
Oh, cool.
Okay, you guys go in there and
confront the Totally Teri
writers.
I'm gonna go find Charles
Dingo's frozen head.
Wait, maybe Freddie
should go with you.
No, I wanna watch Sam
beat up TV writers.
Carly and I got this.
Besides, they ripped off
our ideas, not yours.
I'm a big part of iCarly too.
Yeah, well, I've never heard
Totally Teri say, "in five, four,
three, two, one."
You don't say the one.
Come on. I gotta go find
Charles Dingo's frozen head.
Please go with him.
Okay.
Be careful.
You too.
Okay. Let's shake 'em up.
What is that?
A sock full of butter.
For what?
For swingin'.
I could brain an elephant
with this thing.
We're not gonna walk in there
and start hitting TV writers
with a big buttery sock.
We're gonna be professional and firm.
Fine.
But if they deny stealing from
iCarly, I'm gonna get swingy
with this thing.
Not unless I say it's okay.
Hello.
You guys are the writers
for Totally Teri?
Yeah.
What do you want?
We're from iCarly.
They know that.
Who do you clowns think you
are, stealin' our ideas?
Whoa.
We've never stolen an idea
from anyone, so why don't you
two little girls just-- Sam.
You're not supposed to get
swingy unless I say it's okay.
Hey, what's in that sock?
Payback.
For what?
For stealing our comedy bits.
Look, we've never even
heard of your Web show.
Oh, you haven't?
No.
Hey.
Here's a flash drive with the
segments from the last two iCarlys
you wanted.
Whoa, it's the iCarly girls.
Man, we all love your Web show.
May I get swingy?
Yes.
[Music]
Just what do you girls want?
We want you to stop
stealing ideas from iCarly
and using them on Totally Teri.
Yeah, why don't you nubs come
up with your own comedy ideas?
Because coming up with ideas is hard.
Anyway, we do come up
with our own ideas.
It was my idea to steal from iCarly.
That was my idea.
Whoa, wait.
I'm the one who showed you guys
iCarly.com in the first place.
Hey.
Oh my God.
[Screaming]
Thank you.
We don't care which
one of you fudge bags
thought of stealing our ideas.
We just want it to stop.
All right, well, which bits
do you think we stole?
Random dancing?
No. We did random jumping.
Which is completely different.
Look, for two years on iCarly,
we've been doing random dancing.
Random debates.
Random pants.
Oh, and what about
"messin' with Lewbert"?
Which you punk-nuts ripped off and
called "messin' with Rupert".
You can't just steal our ideas,
change 'em a little bit,
then pretend they're yours.
You said we could.
Shut up.
Anyway, just because we do
some things on Totally Teri
that are similar to the
stuff you do on iCarly...
...
doesn't mean we're stealing.
Then how do you explain
these cards on the wall
under a sign that says "ideas
we can steal from iCarly"?
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
We're not goin' anywhere
till you men swear
to quit rippin' us off.
We don't have to swear anything.
Then we'll Sue you guys.
Uh, this is the Dingo channel.
So, we have the lawyers,
the money, and therefore,
the power to steal any ideas we want.
And there's nothing
you can do about it.
Now, do you ladies
wanna walk out of here
or do you wanna be carried out?
Let's go.
Wait.
What?
I'd kinda like to be carried out.
Sam?
Well, I don't like
walking long distances.
Come on, let's go, come on.
I don't.
There is too much effort, really.
Are you guys writing
down what we're saying?
Yeah, you guys are hilarious.
Now keep talkin'.
This is gold.
They're stealing our banter
right in front of us.
Let's get out of here.
[Music]
No, you just come with me, young man.
You're in serious trouble.
Hey, hey.
You're not supposed to be down here.
Excuse me, but I work
in this building,
and I just caught this boy lurking
here in the bowels of Dingo.
Look, nobody's supposed
to be down on this floor.
Exactly.
So why didn't you stop this
teenager from being here?
Well, I-- I didn't know
he was-- you didn't know.
Isn't it your job to know what's
happening in these hallways?
Yeah, sure, but I-- I
guess I'll have to speak
to Mr. Fufferman about this.
Who's Mr. Fufferman?
Man, what else don't you know?
I-- dismissed.
Go.
Okay, okay.
Wait. I'll need your keys.
Why?
For Mr. Fufferman.
All right, here. Here.
Nice.
Thanks.
Whoa, check it out.
Charles Dingo's head is in there.
You don't know that.
What else would you keep in a
cryogenic freezer like that?
Cryogenic frozen pizzas?
You're afraid to see the head.
I am not.
Good.
[Music]
I'm goin' in.
What do you see?
Nothing. Hold on.
There's a shelf here.
Wait, what's this?
[Screams]
What?
Head, the head. Saw the head.
You did not.
I did too.
It was in a weird,
futuristic head container.
Come on.
Okay, you go in there and
tell me that's not the head
of Charles Dingo--
unless you're scared.
Just wait here.
Okay, the only thing I see
in here is-- [Screams]
It's the head.
It's the head, right?
The head.
Yes, the head.
[Music]
I can't believe we found the head.
I swear it blinked at me.
Would you guys quit talkin'
about the stupid frozen head?
Don't you guys care that those
Dingo writers are gonna keep
ripping off iCarly and there's
nothing we can do about it.
They probably even-- [Squeaking]
[Screams]
What?
A mouse just ran across my foot.
See, he's right over there.
[Squeaking]
That's not a mouse.
That's a rat.
This motel is disgusting.
>>H, you're such a bunch of prancies.
Come on.
These pillows aren't even pillows.
They're just pillow cases
filled with crumpled up
old newspapers.
And this lamp doesn't
even have a light bulb.
Just a potato.
I'm gonna go wash my hands.
Hey, you.
[Screams]
Hobo in our bathtub.
[Music]
Ow.
Scram. Scram. Scram. Scram.
Scram. Scram.
Let's just go home.
And let those Dingo writers
keep stealin' our bits
and using 'em on Totally Teri?
Well, what are we gonna do?
They're the Dingo channel.
They've got money and
lawyers and all we've got
is Sam's butter sock.
We've got the key to the head.
Oh, no.
The head.
[Screams]
[Music]
Move. Move.
Hey.
I was in the middle of my solo.
How'd they get back in here?
Glenn, call security.
Sit down, Glenn!
Now, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Are you gonna stop stealing ideas
from iCarly and using them
on your dumb Dingo show?
Hey, I got it.
What if we do an episode where
someone steals Teri's ideas,
and then she and her
friends-- stop that!
You guys are the worst.
We told you.
You can't stop us from
doing whatever we want.
Can't we?
Spencer.
What's he got there?
Oh, you know, just the...
Frozen head of Charles Dingo.
Hey, no one's supposed
to know about the head.
How did you get it?
You don't need to know.
All you need to do is swear on video
that you'll never steal an
idea from iCarly, ever again.
And what if we don't swear?
Then we'll show Charles
Dingo's head on iCarly.
And tell the whole world that
the Totally Teri writers
gave it to us.
And what if we call
security and have 'em
take the head away from you?
Then we'll just show the
high-rez pics of the head
we already took.
How high-rez?
19 megapixels.
Oh my God.
That's very high-rez.
And we'll be sure to thank
the Totally Teri writers
for e-mailing the pics to us.
We don't care.
We'll get fired.
Don't tell them that.
Just promise u'er steal ideas from
iCarly again and you can have
your leader's head back.
And we'll never say a word about this.
Better hurry, I think Mr.
Dingo's melting.
We swear we'll never steal
ideas from iCarly ever again.
Good.
Give 'em the head.
[Music]
Wait.
What?
You clowns aren't gettin'
off the hook so easy.
Sam.
What else do you want?
And next on iCarly... it's time for...
Bikini dog food fights.
Ready, Dingo boys?
Set... go.
Go.
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0